{"questions":[

  {"questiontext":"Port 20",
    "answerchoice1":"FTP",
    "answerchoice2":"SSH",
    "answerchoice3":"Telnet",
    "answerchoice4":"DNS",
    "answer":1},

  {"questiontext":"Port 21",
    "answerchoice1":"FTP",
    "answerchoice2":"SSH",
    "answerchoice3":"Telnet",
    "answerchoice4":"DNS",
    "answer":1},

  {"questiontext":"Port 22",
    "answerchoice1":"FTP",
    "answerchoice2":"SSH",
    "answerchoice3":"Telnet",
    "answerchoice4":"DNS",
    "answer":2},

  {"questiontext":"Port 23",
    "answerchoice1":"FTP",
    "answerchoice2":"SSH",
    "answerchoice3":"Telnet",
    "answerchoice4":"DNS",
    "answer":3},

  {"questiontext":"Port 53",
    "answerchoice1":"FTP",
    "answerchoice2":"SSH",
    "answerchoice3":"Telnet",
    "answerchoice4":"DNS",
    "answer":4},

  {"questiontext":"Port 66",
    "answerchoice1":"DHCP",
    "answerchoice2":"SMTP",
    "answerchoice3":"POP3",
    "answerchoice4":"IMAP",
    "answer":1},

  {"questiontext":"Port 67",
    "answerchoice1":"DHCP",
    "answerchoice2":"SMTP",
    "answerchoice3":"POP3",
    "answerchoice4":"IMAP",
    "answer":1},

  {"questiontext":"Port 25",
    "answerchoice1":"DHCP",
    "answerchoice2":"SMTP",
    "answerchoice3":"POP3",
    "answerchoice4":"IMAP",
    "answer":2},

  {"questiontext":"Port 110",
    "answerchoice1":"DHCP",
    "answerchoice2":"SMTP",
    "answerchoice3":"POP3",
    "answerchoice4":"IMAP",
    "answer":3},

  {"questiontext":"Port 143",
    "answerchoice1":"DHCP",
    "answerchoice2":"SMTP",
    "answerchoice3":"POP3",
    "answerchoice4":"IMAP4",
    "answer":4},

  {"questiontext":"Port 119",
    "answerchoice1":"IMAP4",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"SNMP",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":4},

  {"questiontext":"Port 161",
    "answerchoice1":"IMAP4",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"SNMP",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":3},

  {"questiontext":"Port 162",
    "answerchoice1":"IMAP4",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"SNMP",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":3},

  {"questiontext":"Port 88",
    "answerchoice1":"L2TP",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"Kerberos",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":3},

  {"questiontext":"Port 1723",
    "answerchoice1":"L2TP",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"Kerberos",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":2},

  {"questiontext":"Port 1701",
    "answerchoice1":"L2TP",
    "answerchoice2":"PPTP",
    "answerchoice3":"Kerberos",
    "answerchoice4":"NNTP",
    "answer":1}

]}